Hello friends, my name is Anil Rajpat,
I am the founder of Family First Financial
Services, MBA Finance, and today I am
presenting before you the
Gold Ultra Plan of ICICI Prudential Life Insurance.
I had made a video on the Gold Video Plan,
and you all
liked it very much. 37,000 people have seen that video so far,
and because this is
not an entertainment video, it is an insurance-
related video, where if we, the
agent, or any insurance seller, go, then the
customer runs away, thinking that there are many agents, let us go and
sell the policy, or else we will go away.
37,000 people have seen the video of the same insurance,
and this plan is selling very well, even when
this plan was launched on
19 January 2023, and even today the
plan is selling very well. If I talk about the
special feature of the Gold Ultra Plan, the feature is that as
I am making the video today, on 25 October
2023, if you purchase the policy today, then on
25 November 2023, next month  You will get the
benefit for the entire year the very next month.
Suppose you are paying Rs 1 lakh,
you will get Rs 1,000 the very next month. This is an
excellent feature which no other company has.
What happens there is that if
you select the monthly mode of income, then you get
that monthly income the next month,
but here you
get the income for the entire year the next month.
So this is an excellent product.
If you want to understand about gold again, then
go to my YouTube2 Triple FS, the
entire video is available there, or
YouTube4 Gold, you will also find my video
in detail. So today's video is
related to Gold Ultra,
how Gold Ultra
can give you extra benefits. In this policy, you will
also get the tax benefit of Section ATC of Income Tax
and all the
survival benefits and maturity covered under 1010D will be tax
free. This policy will run for 100
years. You will start getting income from the first month.
And from day one, you will have
insurance cover through out 100 years.
So watch this video completely. If you like the video, then
like, share and subscribe to my youtube2 Triple FS
and share this video
with as many people as possible.
Thank you. Now let's see, there is a
Gold plan of ICICI Prudential Life Insurance. There is
an option called Ultra Gold in it. I will
try to explain to you how it
works and how you can avail its benefits.
Earlier, I have already
made a video on Gold and you
can watch that video in full detail.
What is there under that plan, for example, if there is a
35 year old person, he is purchasing a policy
where he is paying ₹ lakh annually
and the policy is running for 12 years. Here
you will see that the customer's age is 35 years and he is 64
years, that is, his policy will run till 19 Rs 99 years
for 12 years and he is paying a premium of Rs lakh
and has taken the plan
ICICI Prudential Gold Plan without
Ultra. So now what is happening here that
They will get income every year, in the
first year
they will get income of Rs. 48000, here you
will see in column number 13 and
you
will see the maturity amount of Rs. 1 crore 67 lakh
6382, so they are getting this maturity amount,
but when will they start getting this,
I will tell you that when the customer
will purchase this policy, from here you will see that the
premium is for 12 years, I am
making this video for you today, the date is 25th
October 2023, so
they paid the premium in October 2023
and they will keep getting income till October 87 and
maturity will come later, that is, their
age will be 99, till then this policy
will run and
they will
start getting income of Rs. 41000, when will this income
come, from October 2024,
that is from next year, you will keep getting Rs. 41000 in your account every year
and
on maturity you will get Rs. 1.93 crore one lakh  That you will
also get maturity. Now if
you purchase ICEC Prudential Gold Ultra and
select the Ultra option,
when you purchase the policy,
tell the agent that I want to purchase Ultra, then he will
give you the Ultra option or if you
want to purchase through me, you can also do it.
So here you will see the difference, I will
tell you right here that the
custom of Rs 1 lakh paid for 12 years is 35,
87, you will keep getting income till 2087
and the policy is running till 99 years,
but now the thing to notice here is
that instead of Rs 41, you will get the
income of Rs 3700, 372, 720, 3720, but this
income will not come to you next year, in the next month itself,
in November 2023, on 25th November 2023, after one month,
you will get Rs 37720 in front of the lakh rupees paid.
ICICI
Potential Gold Plan was launched in January 2023
and those who bought the
policy through the Ultra option  Those who have made the purchase, the
amount that was mentioned in their account has
already been credited to everyone's account, so
you will be happy to know that you will get
back 37 against lakh, now you will get 63000 from your pocket
and this policy is going to run for 100 years,
now I am telling you another option
where you can take booster benefit, this
without ultra, I am telling you the booster benefit
that the customer has paid one lakh for
12 years, his age is 35, it is going till 99 years,
but the customer has selected guaranteed booster, the
booster
gives you extra income every 5 years, so here
you will get a guaranteed extra income of Rs 1000 220,
I will show you how here, you
see in column number four, you will get Rs 13250 in every 5 years
gap, on
which guarantee is also written, this
additional income will keep coming, so here the
income of Rs 41000 is coming in column number 13,
every 5 years  Later you will see that you are getting an income of Rs 54000, Rs
5250, Rs
5250, so if you
want to get more income for yourself during your lifetime, then you can take it
and on maturity you will also get Rs 1.3 crore,
you can take this booster option in Ultra also,
in Ultra also if you make this
purchase by selecting Ultra option, then you will
see that
you are getting an
income of Rs 3720 from November 2023 and
you will keep getting Rs 12190 guaranteed in the gap of every pa year,
so here you
see 12190, here you will
see 4990 in front of 3720 after the gap of every pa year,
so in this way you will get extra income every pa year
and you will
also get Rs 1.34 cr on maturity,
you paid the premium, on 25 October 2023
when did the money come back to your account, on 25 November
2023 after one month you would have got the benefit of the entire year
If you want immediate income,
early income and
income for life time, then you
can purchase this policy. You will get income for life time, you will
also have life time insurance
cover,
maturity will also be tax free in the income tax section and
you will also get tax benefit in ATC. So
if you watched the video and liked it, then while
leaving, definitely
like, share and subscribe to my channel. And
if you want to know about this type of
plan where you get income from the first month and the
policy runs for 100 years, then which other
company has this type of plan, does ADFC have this type of
plan, does Tata have this type of plan, does
Maths have this type of plan, does
Bajaj have this type of plan, if yes then you can get the
highest
returns by comparing, for all this information
you can give me my information as well as
in the comment box and
if you want to purchase the policy by comparing, then
contact me on
9094 3412.  Thank you so much Jai
Hind